Hello.
Thank you.
Look at the camera.
You know
what your answer should be, don't you?
Will you marry me?
Say yes! Say yes!
Marry him! Marry him!
Yes, I do!
She said 'yes'.
Now, you two get the hell out of here.
Go!
I came here with Eva,
and I'm leaving with her.
She will be my wife soon.
Weechana.
If we're serious about getting married,
you need to stop doing this.
I still need to work with them.
I've already found someone to replace them.
Weechana?
I'm working on finding you a new manager.
For now, let Pat handle things.
As for these two bastards,
just let them go.
But...
We're done here, aren't we?
Shall we head home?
I can take you to see your aunt.
You'd like to see her, wouldn't you?
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go.
Don't let them follow us.
Go.
We should go.
How many times are you gonna come at us
and lose?
You never learn, do you?
Next time, wait until we actually win
before you start bragging.
You're right.
It'll be so embarrassing if we lose.
We're not gonna lose, man.
I'm sorry.
Boat!
Come here.
Hurry. Come on.
Auntie!
Auntie.
How are you?
I'm okay. You?
I'm okay.
Eva, come on.
Do you really think I'm such a bad person?
I'm begging you. Please leave my aunt alone.
I haven't done anything.
I just brought you here so you and your aunt
could pack your things and come live with me.
Aunt Da.
I need to ask you a favor.
You need to stop selling food.
Okay?
Go pack your things.
I...
Can you give me three days?
Everything's happening so fast,
and I haven't had time
to get everything in order yet.
I've actually got everything ready for you
at my place.
There's a gym, a personal trainer,
and a tutor.
They're all ready to start.
If you need any clothes or anything else,
I can just buy you new ones.
It's not about that.
I'm going to be really busy
for the next few days.
If I have to spend time packing,
I won't have time to get myself ready.
And I need time to adjust, too.
I want everyone to see
that it is all over now.
There's nothing going on anymore,
so we can all move on.
Foreign film crews
don't want to deal with this kind of drama.
They think it's unprofessional.
I want to show them that I'm ready.
And I need to show them
that I'm the best choice.
All right, then.
I'll give you one day.
I'll come pick you up tomorrow.
And like I said,
if you need anything, just tell me.
I'll take care of it.
Anything you want,
except Pun.
Are we clear?
Yes.
Thank you.
Good girl.
Let's go.
Keep an eye on her from a distance
until tomorrow.
If that bastard Pun shows his face again,
take care of him.
Yes, sir.
Let's look around this place.
Auntie, hurry up and pack.
Take only what you need.
- We have to get out of here.
- Okay.
Oh, it's you.
You can't leave yet.
Weechana has his men watching the place.
Thank you.
I didn't think you two would actually come.
I will never leave you.
It's going to be okay.
Weechana can send as many men as he wants.
They still won't be able to beat us.
Don't you worry.
You...
Are you two really okay?
We're okay.
Are you and your aunt okay?
What about Grandpa Rueang?
Did he come to keep you company?
They kicked him out, shut down the shop,
and forced me at gunpoint to call her.
So that's why you said yes?
That's right.
Damn.
How can he be such a fucking asshole?
Where are you running to?
I don't know, but I have to get out of here.
Once he gets me into his house,
I know I won't be able to leave.
Then you and your aunt
should go pack your things.
I'll call Ekachai and see if he can help us.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
[Weechana surprises Eva
with a proposal at an event.]
What is going on?
I said he could propose to her, but not now!
You're starting to lose your grip
on Weechana.
Did you know about this?
I'm supposed to be the distraction,
not the one creating the problem.
Then go create a distraction.
We don't need to do anything about it.
Hey, what is your plan?
I thought your dad told you
to stick to the plan from now on.
- What the hell is this?
- Nothing's gone off-plan, Grandma.
And you're the one who approved it.
The marriage is supposed
to bury the Domino story,
not distract people from the campaign.
We have to make the public see
that their concerns are our highest priority.
And after this, who's going to trust us?
Where the hell is she?
She said yes to marrying you.
So why haven't you brought her home?
She said she needed some time to get ready,
so I gave her until tomorrow.
What does she need so much time
to prepare for?
After the proposal,
I saw you had people
take care of everything for her.
She has her aunt, and her work.
- And you believed her?
- I sent my guys to watch her.
For God's sake!
Can you just be a normal grandma
and do what grandmas do?
Go knit or play bingo.
Let me deal with this.
Weechana!
Whoa, bro!
Listen!
If you won't take my advice,
then you'd better know what you're doing.
If you screw this up,
I'll have all your heads.
I know, I know.
I'll apologize later.
Weechana.
Are you sure Eva won't try to leave?
Got it.
Thank you so much.
Let me help you with that.
Thanks.
What did he say?
He'll be here soon with another cop,
but all they can do is distract them.
We'll have to use that chance
to escape through the back of the shop.
You hold on to the car keys.
We'll go with Aunt Da
and take everything with us.
If you and your aunt get to the car first
and anything happens,
drive away immediately.
Don't wait for us. We'll be fine.
Ekachai will be there with us.
Do you know where you'll go?
I have no idea.
Probably a hotel somewhere out of town.
It's too much traffic.
Someone could recognize you.
If you and your aunt don't mind,
I know a place.
A friend of mine moved back here
after he got married
and opened a café in Khao Yai.
He's got a place we can stay.
It's private and low-key.
We could go there, if you're okay with it.
Okay, let's go there.
Good. I'll let him know right now.
Eva, I think you should leave without me.
I don't want to be a burden.
No. We have to go together.
If you stay here, they'll just take you.
I know about that.
I'll just be a burden if I go with you.
Auntie.
You've never been a burden to me.
I'm the one who's put you through all this.
[We're here.]
Standby.
I hate to rush you,
but we need to get out of here.
Please come with us.
- But...
- How about this?
We all leave together,
then you can drop Aunt Da and me off
at my place in Saraburi first.
My mom runs a small restaurant there.
Aunt Da can stay with us, no problem.
And I'll stay with her so she won't be alone.
Sounds good?
Please come with us, Auntie.
My mom's cooking is just as good as yours.
Okay?
Fine, I'm coming with you.
- Let's go.
- Hurry!
What are you doing here?
You've been lurking around here,
watching someone else's house.
You're freaking out the neighbors.
That's why they called the cops.
Exactly.
He said you're not from around here.
Wait a second.
You two look familiar.
I feel like I've seen you somewhere before.
Let me check.
Do you have a record?
They are working for me.
Is everything okay.
Eva told me she's been feeling uneasy
because someone's been stalking her lately.
So I had my men keep an eye on her place.
Which house reported them, Captain?
Will you excuse me?
[Weechana's at the front.
His men are at the back.]
Let's go.
Watch your step.
Weechana's waiting out front
while his men head around back.
Boat, if I don't come back in 20 minutes,
take my aunt and go without me.
Got it. Let's go.
Hurry up! Come on.
Eva.
Eva!
Open it!
Hurry up.
You can't get in, sir.
You know this is trespassing, right?
What trespassing?
I have a key.
I just sent my men to unlock the back door.
That's all.
What you're doing isn't legal.
I can arrest you for this.
Stay out of it.
Quit sticking your nose in,
or you might end up with more than
just a suspension. You want to find out?
Are you sure about that?
I can vouch for Captain Ekachai.
He was just doing his job.
Don't you have families
you should be thinking about?
Don't you?
They are not upstairs, sir.
It's none of your business.
I'm about to become part of this family.
I have every right to keep people out.
Anyone goes in,
I'll have them charged with trespassing too.
You.
Trust me when I say your families
will face an even worse fate.
Just pretend you didn't see it.
Go.
Just go!
You need to check outside.
And you, go upstairs and search again.
Check every damn corner.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
[Weechana, monster from hell]
Fuck!
What?
All clear!
[Welcome to Saraburi]
They are not here, sir.
- They are not upstairs either.
- No?
Goddammit!
You can't even find them?
Huh?
Aunt Da, let's go.
Be careful.
Auntie.
As soon as I get a new phone,
I'll get in touch with you.
If there's anything you need or want,
just tell Boat.
He'll let me know.
- Sure.
- Don't worry about me.
You need to worry about yourself.
I'm worried about you. He'll come after you.
Just stay safe and come back for me.
I'll be here waiting for you.
I'll be back soon. I promise.
I'll wait here.
Go on, get going before I start tearing up.
Please take care of Eva.
Don't worry. I'll take good care of her.
- Please take care of my aunt.
- Sure, don't worry.
I'll see you later.
My friend, my friend.
- Jimmy.
- Long time no see.
- I'm really glad you came.
- Nice to see you, man.
Is this your girlfriend? Hi.
I'm Jim. Nice to meet you.
Hi, I'm Eva. Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Pun's friend.
Just friends... for now?
Okay, okay. Enough with the teasing.
Seriously, though,
thank you for letting us stay here.
- We're really in trouble.
- Yeah, no worries.
But I do have to let you know one thing.
I only have one guest room,
and you guys will have to share it.
But the good news is
that it'll be just you two.
The restaurant
gets customers sometimes but...
it's in a different area.
Okay.
Well, he said...
It's okay. I think I got what he said.
He said there's only one guest room
in his house,
so we'll probably have to share.
And good news is the café
and the house are separate,
so we'll still have some privacy.
That's pretty much it, right?
Yeah, you got all of that right.
I'm impressed.
Okay. Thank you for letting us stay.
I really mean it.
And thanks for speaking in a way
that I can actually understand.
What? What do you mean?
No, it wasn't him.
It's you.
He spoke normally.
You're just getting better.
Darling.
Why didn't you tell me
your friends had arrived?
Oh, my beautiful wife!
Come meet my friends.
Hello.
Jim, you never told me
your friend was famous!
- Are you Eva?
- Yes, that's me.
My name is Joy. I'm such a huge fan.
I can't believe I'm meeting you in person!
Can I get a picture with you?
Sure.
Would you mind not posting it, though?
Oh, I heard about that.
If I were you, I'd run too.
He is a powerful man.
Thank you.
Come on, let's go inside. It's hot out here.
Darling, do you want me
to make dinner for your friends?
No, you don't have too.
This is one of the best cooks I know.
- Really?
- We'll let him handle it.
My goodness.
Sounds delicious. I want to try it.
What he said...
about us having to share a room.
Oh, I forgot.
I was just impressed that you understood him.
Jim.
Okay, you sleep in here.
I'll take the couch in the living room.
No, it's okay. This is your friend's place.
I'll take the couch.
Back when I was an extra,
I had it way tougher than this.
It's okay. It's been a long drive.
Besides, you're the lady.
You should take the bed.
Can you taste this for me?
What do you think?
Whoa!
Wow, this is incredible!
Hey.
You don't have to teach me English anymore,
you know.
You should open a restaurant instead.
You're exaggerating.
Hey, I am not exaggerating.
I've eaten at some
really good restaurants abroad,
and none of them were as good as yours.
You should open a restaurant.
Have you ever tasted me?
I'm talking about your cooking skill.
Actually, like I told you before,
when this is all over,
I think I'll open my own restaurant.
I've managed to save up some money.
Enough for a small place, I think.
Yeah, you should do that.
I will be rooting for you.
One more bite?
Yes, please.
You should try the chicken.
What?
- Let's try the chicken.
- You're not tasting your food?
Any notes? Should I add anything?
Why don't you team up with my aunt?
Working with Aunt Da?
Great idea.
- Fusion food.
- What should we name it?
- Aunt Da...
- Da-Pun? Pun-Da?
Oh my goodness! No.
Wow, it looks so good.
- Alright.
- Here you go.
Wow!
That looks so good.
Thank you.
- Thank you for this meal.
- Yeah, thank you very much.
You're very welcome.
Hey. Cheers?
- Cheers!
How does it taste?
- Really nice.
- This bottle's been aged for years.
Alright, let's dig in!
Several events have been unable to reach Eva
through any channel today.
What are your thoughts on that?
I'm worried about her
because I still haven't been able
to reach her myself.
Darling?
Everyone, look.
What do you have to say
about the rumors
that Eva disappeared
after agreeing to marry you?
[Eva goes missing after skipping events.]
I honestly don't know either.
But Eva has never done
anything like this before.
Do you think
this has anything to do
with the man Eva's been seen with lately?
Come to think of it,
Eva's life has been a mess
ever since he came into the picture.
Just look at what happened
in that last video.
Could Pun have something to do
with Eva's disappearance?
I wouldn't go so far as to say that.
But one thing I'm sure of
is that Eva isn't safe with him.
If anyone happens to see the man I mentioned,
Pun Punnathorn Jiraworameta,
please notify the police or contact my party.